Mobina Jamali

■ mobiina.jamali@gmail.com 🤳 587-438-6550 🛅 LinkedIn 🗘 GitHub 🏶 Portfolio Website

SKILLS: PyTorch, , TensorFlow, ROS, Linux, GIT, Reinforcement Learning, OpenCV,

Pandas, SQL, Gazebo, OOP, TDD

LANGUAGES/ ENVS: Python, C++, HTML/CSS

SUMMARY

I am a roboticist and AI researcher working on Multi-Agent Reinforcement Learning. My research focuses on developing autonomous agents capable of collaborating with human in executing complex, multi-step tasks by integrating learning and planning strategies.

EDUCATION

University of Calgary

2018 - 2023

Bachelor of Science, Physics

· Thesis: "Advancing the Control for a Highly Maneuverable Autonomous Underwater Vehicle (HM-AUV)", advised by Dr. Alex Ramirez-Serrano.

EXPERIENCE

Intelligent Robot Learning Lab (IRL), University of Alberta

July 2024 - Present

Research Intern Supervisor: Matthew Taylor

- · Working on agent interactions and peer-to-peer knowledge exchange techniques in Multi Agent System (MAS), especially on how to enable RL agents learn effectively through various teacher-student interaction modalities.
- · Developing and integrating pessimistic advising in MAS, focusing on guiding agents away from suboptimal actions.
- · Implementing the Upper Confidence Bound (UCB) algorithm to measure uncertainty in agent decision-making to identify optimal moments for seeking guidance.

Unmanned Vehicles Robotarium Lab, University of Calgary

September 2022 - April 2023

Undergraduate Research Assistant

Supervisor: Alex Ramirez-Serrano

- · Developed a dynamic model and control scheme for a three-thruster configuration AUV, enabling the vehicle to have full autonomy over its 6 DOF.
- · Performed comprehensive simulations to validate the AUV's capability for precise navigation, achieving 83% success in complex maneuvering across diverse scenarios.

Quantum Cloud Lab, University of Calgary

April 2022 - September 2022

Undergraduate Research Assistant

Supervisors: Daniel Oblak, Vahid Salari

- · Utilized Photo-Multiplier Tube (PMT), and Superconducting Nanowire Single-Photon Detector (SNSPD) to detect Ultra-weak Photon Emission (UPE) in tadpole models.
- · Co-authored a review paper, Advances in Sensing and Imaging Biological Ultra-weak Photon Emission, currently under review at Optica journal.

TEACHING

Faculty of Physics and Astronomy, University of Calgary

January 2022 - April 2022

Undergraduate Teaching Assistant

- · Collaborated with professors to create organized and engaging course materials for PHYS 229 (Modern Physics) and PHYS 259 (Electricity and Magnetism).
- \cdot Assisted more than 120 students with course content and answering their questions.

PUBLICATION

 $Orbit\ Determination\ Lead$

Advances in Sensing and Imaging Biological Ultraweak Photon Emission Vahid Salari, <u>Mobina Jamali</u> , Daniel Oblak	Under Review Optica Journal
SCHOLARSHIP AND AWARD	
- Program for Undergraduate Research Experience (PURE) - \$7500	March 2022
- University of Calgary Summer Research Funding, NSRS - \$6000	April 2019
- President's Admission Scholarship - \$5000	Auguest 2018
PROFESSIONAL DEVELOPEMENT	
University of California San Diego	2023 - 2024
MicroMaster's Program, Data Science	
EXTRA-CURRICULAR ACTIVITY	

 \cdot Led University of Calgary's first 3U CubeSat design, operations, and mission planning.

Calgary To Space Organization, University of Calgary

· Organized "Women in Space" sessions and spearheaded outreach campaigns to inspire high school students about satellites and space technology.

May 2021 - April 2023